<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/">
<channel>
<title>IT Security Guru</title>
<atom:link href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<link>https://www.itsecurityguru.org/</link>
<description>The Site for our Community</description>
<lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 16:19:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
<language>en-US</language>
<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
<image>
<url>https://www.itsecurityguru.org/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/cropped-Guru_Transparent-PNG-1-32x32.png</url>
<title>IT Security Guru</title>
<link>https://www.itsecurityguru.org/</link>
<width>32</width>
<height>32</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Cato Networks再次被评为SASE领先者</title>
<link>https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/21/cato-networks-named-sase-leader-again/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=cato-networks-named-sase-leader-again</link>
<dc:creator>Tara Antoni</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 16:19:38 +0000</pubDate>
<category>Featured</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.itsecurityguru.org/?p=50458</guid>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Today, Cato Networks, announced its recognition as a Leader in both the Frost Radar™: Global SASE, 2023 by Frost &amp;#38; Sullivan and the Market Radar: SASE 2023 by Omdia. “Once again, Cato Networks and our cloud-native SASE platform have been recognised by the industry for its innovation and leadership,” said Shlomo Kramer, founder and CEO [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/21/cato-networks-named-sase-leader-again/"&gt;Cato Networks Named SASE Leader, Again&lt;/a&gt; first appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/21/cato-networks-named-sase-leader-again/"&gt;Cato Networks Named SASE Leader, Again&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
<content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Today, &lt;a href="https://www.catonetworks.com/"&gt;Cato Networks&lt;/a&gt;, announced its recognition as a Leader in both the &lt;em&gt;Frost Radar&lt;img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /&gt;: Global SASE, 2023&lt;/em&gt; by Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan and the &lt;em&gt;Market Radar: SASE 2023&lt;/em&gt; by Omdia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Once again, Cato Networks and our cloud-native SASE platform have been recognised by the industry for its innovation and leadership,” said Shlomo Kramer, founder and CEO of Cato Networks. “These distinctions from Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan and Omdia echo what we consistently hear from the thousands of organisations that secure their future with Cato every day.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan and Omdia honours underscore Cato Networks’ consistent excellence in growth and innovation and comes after the Cato SASE Cloud was recognised by other leading research firms in 2023.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Omdia: Cato is a Leader with a Strong Alignment of Business Model to SASE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Omdia &lt;em&gt;Market Radar: SASE &lt;/em&gt;assesses SASE offerings from more than 30 technology vendors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cato Networks emerged as distinct market leader in Omdia’s analysis, leading in several categories including security (SWG, ZTA, and CASB), networking (architecture and SD-WAN), and management (identity and analytics). Omdia’s assessment supports Cato’s consistent and advanced capabilities, positioning it as a, “&amp;#8230;Leader, with strong alignment of business model to SASE with a robust architecture within its PoPs and delivery of core networking and security services.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cato Networks showcased advanced capabilities across various SASE categories,” said Fernando Montenegro, Senior Principal Analyst, Cybersecurity, of Omdia. “Their holistic approach, combined with efficient delivery and a focus on offering SASE as a true service, makes them a strong contender for organisations looking for a comprehensive SASE cloud offering.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan: Cato is Committed to Innovation and Excellence&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Frost Radar&lt;img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /&gt; for SASE evaluates SASE companies based on their continuous innovation and ability to translate innovations into consistent growth. Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan recognises Cato as a growth and innovation leader in SASE, placing Cato highest on the Frost Radar Innovation Index. Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan also cited Cato Networks as a single-vendor SASE provider that is excelling in both domains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cato Networks topped the Frost Radar Innovation Index and is a leader on the Frost Radar Growth Index. The company’s commitment to sustained excellence in the SASE market is evident through its purpose-built cloud-first and converged SASE platform. Cato Networks’ global private backbone, extensive SASE PoPs coverage across regions, and single-pass architecture powered by the Cato Single Pass Cloud Engine (SPACE) demonstrate its innovation leadership to deliver global, converged, cloud-native networking and security services to enterprises,” said Vivien Pua, senior industry analyst at Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information about Cato Networks’ ranking, download Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan’s &lt;em&gt;Frost Radar&lt;img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /&gt;: Global SASE, 2023 &lt;/em&gt;report &lt;a href="https://usw2.nyl.as/t1/95/8xmuphtk0eeue6svr88wuj7m5/1/b735b316e27ec19d0243763126f5844c9657469ead4f9e4ca7a29f50bdbbee2a"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/21/cato-networks-named-sase-leader-again/"&gt;Cato Networks Named SASE Leader, Again&lt;/a&gt; first appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/21/cato-networks-named-sase-leader-again/"&gt;Cato Networks Named SASE Leader, Again&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded>
</item>
<item>
<title>本周，Lookout提醒美国员工和企业注意重大的网络钓鱼威胁。</title>
<link>https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/21/lookout-alerts-u-s-employees-and-businesses-of-significant-phishing-threat-this-week/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=lookout-alerts-u-s-employees-and-businesses-of-significant-phishing-threat-this-week</link>
<dc:creator>Tara Antoni</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 14:35:33 +0000</pubDate>
<category>Featured</category>
<category>Features</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.itsecurityguru.org/?p=50453</guid>
<description>&lt;p&gt;This week, Lookout, Inc., is warning employees and businesses that phishing attacks across enterprise and personal devices are expected to more than double this week, based on historical data. With more corporate data residing in the cloud today and an increased number of employees working remotely, mobile has become the endpoint of choice for the [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/21/lookout-alerts-u-s-employees-and-businesses-of-significant-phishing-threat-this-week/"&gt;Lookout Alerts U.S. Employees and Businesses of Significant Phishing Threat This Week&lt;/a&gt; first appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/21/lookout-alerts-u-s-employees-and-businesses-of-significant-phishing-threat-this-week/"&gt;Lookout Alerts U.S. Employees and Businesses of Significant Phishing Threat This Week&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
<content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;This week, &lt;a href="https://www.lookout.com/"&gt;Lookout, Inc&lt;/a&gt;., is warning employees and businesses that phishing attacks across enterprise and personal devices are expected to more than double this week, based on historical data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With more corporate data residing in the cloud today and an increased number of employees working remotely, mobile has become the endpoint of choice for the modern workforce. However, since these devices have traditionally been neglected as part of a company’s overall security strategy, they have also become the most susceptible target for external hackers to gain access to corporate cloud infrastructure through social engineering and credential theft.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the busy Black Friday shopping week, the risk of being targeted by a malicious phishing campaign only increases as employees are more distracted and moving quickly to get the best deals on their holiday purchases. This creates a perfect opportunity for potential hackers to carry out socially engineered phishing attacks that can lead to credential theft and direct access to sensitive corporate data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The warning comes as new Lookout research reveals that:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Three in five employees (63%) admit that they are more distracted during Thanksgiving week as they juggle work and play during the holiday.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The vast majority of employees (89%) will capitalise on Black Friday and Cyber Monday sales with more than half (57%) admitting they are more likely to click on unfamiliar links in search of good deals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two-thirds of employees (66%) will shop on personal mobile phones which are notoriously overlooked in security planning – in fact, nearly half of workers (47%) reported their employer provides no mobile security platform for device protection.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The research finds that the most popular social media apps that will be used on mobile by employees this week are Facebook (76%), Instagram (63%) and TikTok (50%).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“&lt;em&gt;As shoppers look to take advantage of the best online sales, fraudsters will do the same. But rather than discounted gifts, the best deal for a cybercriminal is access to corporate data that can then be distorted and/or sold for huge sums of money,” said &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/davidlukerichardson/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;David Richardson&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;, Vice President of Endpoint and Threat Intelligence&lt;/em&gt;, Lookout.&lt;em&gt; “A popular technique is to target employees on their mobile devices through social engineering – dodging traditional enterprise security protection by messaging the victim via their personal messaging accounts. Last year, we saw a huge spike in phishing rates. As employees are distracted by shopping on their mobile device, CISOs face a significant phishing risk. But rather than just focusing on the particular methods attackers may use this Thanksgiving, businesses should take a data-centric approach and monitor for changes in user behaviour and anomalous data transfers.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The survey follows the &lt;a href="https://www.lookout.com/documents/reports/Global-State-of-Mobile-Phishing-Report.pdf?utm_medium=asset&amp;amp;utm_source=phishing-infographic"&gt;2022 Lookout Global State of Mobile Phishing Report&lt;/a&gt; which found:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In 2022, more than 50% of personal devices were exposed to a mobile phishing attack every quarter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The percentage of users falling for multiple mobile phishing links in a year is increasing rapidly year over year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organisations that operate in highly regulated industries – including insurance, banking, legal, healthcare and financial services – were the most heavily targeted enterprises.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/21/lookout-alerts-u-s-employees-and-businesses-of-significant-phishing-threat-this-week/"&gt;Lookout Alerts U.S. Employees and Businesses of Significant Phishing Threat This Week&lt;/a&gt; first appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/21/lookout-alerts-u-s-employees-and-businesses-of-significant-phishing-threat-this-week/"&gt;Lookout Alerts U.S. Employees and Businesses of Significant Phishing Threat This Week&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded>
</item>
<item>
<title>LummaC2 Stealer的新的反沙箱技术？三角学</title>
<link>https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/20/lummac2-stealers-new-anti-sandbox-technique-trigonometry/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=lummac2-stealers-new-anti-sandbox-technique-trigonometry</link>
<dc:creator>Guru Writer</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 14:41:21 +0000</pubDate>
<category>Threat Detection</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.itsecurityguru.org/?p=50436</guid>
<description>&lt;p&gt;New research by Outpost24 has revealed that malware developers are using sandbox evasion techniques to avoid exposing malicious behaviour inside a sandbox where malware is analysed by security researches. Outpost24’s threat intelligence team, KrakenLabs, discovered that malware developers are using trigonometry to detect human behaviour based on cursor positions to avoid automated security analysis. The Malware-as-a-Service (MaaS) [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/20/lummac2-stealers-new-anti-sandbox-technique-trigonometry/"&gt;LummaC2 Stealer’s New Anti-Sandbox Technique? Trigonometry&lt;/a&gt; first appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/20/lummac2-stealers-new-anti-sandbox-technique-trigonometry/"&gt;LummaC2 Stealer&amp;#8217;s New Anti-Sandbox Technique? Trigonometry&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
<content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://usw2.nyl.as/t1/302/7fuj9cqnv8dbqw42rqztmkovi/1/964d17233cb97ada37bae00e562371b8acd5b22c5191c7ed61b3c2212607293c"&gt;New research&lt;/a&gt; by &lt;a href="https://usw2.nyl.as/t1/302/7fuj9cqnv8dbqw42rqztmkovi/0/d9226053512ece18a749a6b77cc909ac41774d8e8a801637171bb962d9223640"&gt;Outpost24&lt;/a&gt; has revealed that malware developers are using sandbox evasion techniques to avoid exposing malicious behaviour inside a sandbox where malware is analysed by security researches. Outpost24’s threat intelligence team, KrakenLabs, discovered that malware developers are using trigonometry to detect human behaviour based on cursor positions to avoid automated security analysis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Malware-as-a-Service (MaaS) model poses a significant threat in the realm of cybersecurity. This model allows individuals or groups with limited technical expertise to access and deploy sophisticated malware tools and services, often developed by more skilled cybercriminals. The ease of access to such malicious tools has contributed to an increase in the number and complexity of cyberattacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anti-analysis techniques have been the bane of many security analysts, as they have been included in malware practically since its inception. As the name implies, these techniques are designed to prevent the analysis and understanding of the software they are meant to protect, typically by making it harder to understand when looking at the &amp;#8220;code&amp;#8221; or by preventing the execution of the malware in controlled environments. Like every other aspect of cybersecurity, malware developers have been playing a game of cat and mouse with security analysts, developing new techniques to detect these environments, while security analysts work on techniques to disable or undo them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since December 2022, LummaC2, an information stealer written in C language, has been sold in underground forums. KrakenLabs previously published an &lt;a href="https://outpost24.com/blog/everything-you-need-to-know-lummac2-stealer/"&gt;in-depth analysis of the malware&lt;/a&gt; assessing LummaC2’s primary workflow, its different obfuscation techniques, and how to overcome them to effectively analyse the malware with ease. The malware has since gone through different updates and is currently on version 4.0. Among other updates, version 4.0 has included a new Anti-Sandbox technique to delay detonation of the sample until human mouse activity is detected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the blog post, published today, the KrakenLabs team deep dive, with highly technical insight, into the Packer, as well as the Control Flow Flattening technique. Control Flow Flattening is an obfuscation technique aimed at breaking the original flow of the program and complicating its analysis. Additionally, it makes use of opaque predicates and dead code to complicate analysis and make identification of relevant blocks more difficult.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LummaC2 v4.0 makes use of a novel anti-sandbox technique that forces the malware to wait until “human” behaviour is detected in the infected machine. This technique takes into consideration different positions of the cursor in a short interval to detect human activity, effectively preventing detonation in most analysis systems that do not emulate mouse movements realistically.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The threat researchers also found that advertisements in underground forums describe protecting the malware with a crypter is recommended to avoid leaking the malware anywhere in its pure form. Newer versions of the malware added a new feature to avoid leaking the unpacked samples.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To protect against threats similar to these, advanced threat detection, alongside user education and regular software updates is key. &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/10/outpost24-core-advancement-delivers-complete-visibility-of-technology-assets-and-threat-exposure/"&gt;Earlier this month,&lt;/a&gt; Outpost24 announced updates to their CORE platform, with complete visibility of technology assets and threat exposure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/20/lummac2-stealers-new-anti-sandbox-technique-trigonometry/"&gt;LummaC2 Stealer’s New Anti-Sandbox Technique? Trigonometry&lt;/a&gt; first appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/20/lummac2-stealers-new-anti-sandbox-technique-trigonometry/"&gt;LummaC2 Stealer&amp;#8217;s New Anti-Sandbox Technique? Trigonometry&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded>
</item>
<item>
<title>识别欺诈模式并防止数据丢失: 一种统一的方法</title>
<link>https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/20/recognising-scam-patterns-and-preventing-data-loss-a-unified-approach/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=recognising-scam-patterns-and-preventing-data-loss-a-unified-approach</link>
<dc:creator>Guru Writer</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 11:41:47 +0000</pubDate>
<category>Insight</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.itsecurityguru.org/?p=50434</guid>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Cybersecurity professionals stand on the frontlines, ever-vigilant against an increasing tide of cyber threats. From protecting sensitive corporate data to safeguarding our personal information, the battle against cybercrime is ongoing. In today&amp;#8217;s digital era, cybercriminals are becoming more sophisticated and professional in their methods. Hybrid work models and broadly adopted cloud technology create highly dispersed [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/20/recognising-scam-patterns-and-preventing-data-loss-a-unified-approach/"&gt;Recognising Scam Patterns and Preventing Data Loss: A Unified Approach&lt;/a&gt; first appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/20/recognising-scam-patterns-and-preventing-data-loss-a-unified-approach/"&gt;Recognising Scam Patterns and Preventing Data Loss: A Unified Approach&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
<content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Cybersecurity professionals stand on the frontlines, ever-vigilant against an increasing tide of cyber threats. From protecting sensitive corporate data to safeguarding our personal information, the battle against cybercrime is ongoing. In today&amp;#8217;s digital era, cybercriminals are becoming more sophisticated and professional in their methods.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hybrid work models and broadly adopted cloud technology create highly dispersed environments that assist bad actors in remaining covered in the shadow and accomplishing malicious acts against businesses of any size and sector. The &lt;a href="https://cybersecurityventures.com/cybercrime-damage-costs-10-trillion-by-2025/"&gt;predictions&lt;/a&gt; are on their side, as more intense and frequent cyber attacks will drive up costs by 15% per year. At the same time, data loss will have serious repercussions, including financial losses ($10.5 trillion in annual costs in 2025), operations disruptions, regulatory fines, and reputational damage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Recognising the threat patterns&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shaping a better cybersecurity future is imperative. Businesses and organisations shall realise the threats, their size and origins. They shall also understand the significance of data loss, the unauthorised or accidental destruction, alteration, or exposure of sensitive information through various means, malicious or erroneous, and the impact on their business.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They must recognise the scam patterns that may threaten a business’s data and take a unified approach to prevent data loss and mitigate cyber threats. Data are vital for an organisation and must be protected against exfiltration and exploitation through the implementation of an adequate &lt;a href="https://www.cyberhaven.com/data-loss-prevention-guide/microsoft-purview-dlp-office-365-overview/"&gt;data loss prevention&lt;/a&gt; (DLP) strategy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spear Phishing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While phishing remains one of the &lt;a href="https://www.graphus.ai/blog/phishing-is-the-biggest-data-loss-threat-that-businesses-face/"&gt;most prevalent&lt;/a&gt; methods cybercriminals use, spear phishing represents a refined form of the traditional phishing technique. Unlike the indiscriminate approach of generic phishing, vishing, and smishing, where malicious actors mimic legitimate communications from trusted entities to prompt a random recipient to click a link, download an attachment, or input sensitive information, spear phishing is highly targeted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cybercriminals invest time and effort to research their intended victim, often a high-profile individual or organisation. By gathering specific information, they craft a meticulously personalised message that appears legitimate, making it exceedingly difficult to distinguish from authentic communication, given their increasing sophistication.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Business Email Compromise (BEC)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BEC attacks have experienced a significant upsurge in recent years. According to &lt;a href="https://abnormalsecurity.com/blog/2022-fbi-ic3-report"&gt;the FBI&lt;/a&gt;, BEC is considered one of the fastest-growing, most financially damaging internet-enabled crimes and has resulted in more than $43 billion in &lt;a href="https://www.cloudflare.com/en-gb/lp/stop-business-email-compromise-threats/"&gt;reported losses&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a BEC attack, malicious actors impersonate high-ranking officials within a company, often assuming the guise of the CEO or CFO to defraud the organisation. These impostors then request financial transactions, divulge sensitive data, or issue instructions that, on the surface, appear legitimate. What makes BEC attacks particularly treacherous is the level of authenticity bad actors project in their communications, including the use of convincing email addresses and &lt;a href="https://privacy-pc.com/articles/your-5-minute-guide-to-insider-threats.html"&gt;insider&lt;/a&gt; knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tech Support Scam&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While they may seem like a relic of the past, tech support scams continue to &lt;a href="https://www.aarp.org/money/scams-fraud/info-2023/fake-online-tech-support.html"&gt;thrive&lt;/a&gt; and deceive numerous victims. In this scheme, cybercriminals pose as tech support agents and contact individuals, claiming a problem exists with their computers. They urgently insist on immediate action, which typically involves payment or granting remote access to the victim&amp;#8217;s device, only to introduce malware or steal data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The psychological manipulation and exploitation of users&amp;#8217; fear and lack of technical knowledge make them particularly susceptible to this type of threat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Malvertising&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Malvertising &lt;a href="https://perception-point.io/guides/cybersecurity/how-to-protect-your-organization-against-malvertising-attacks/"&gt;is a tactic&lt;/a&gt; where cybercriminals exploit online advertising networks to disseminate malicious advertisements. Unsuspecting users who click these malevolent ads may unknowingly download malware or ransomware onto their devices. Via malvertising, bad actors frequently leverage users&amp;#8217; trust in well-known websites, adding a layer of deception to their attacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;A prevention approach&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A multi-layered approach is essential for businesses to defend against the multifaceted threats. That unified strategy shall include the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Continuous Education and Training: &lt;/strong&gt;No matter how robust your technical defences are, human is the most critical cybersecurity factor, as it involves mental processes, perception, reluctance, ignorance, and mood swings. As human errors have always been a significant cybersecurity risk and vulnerability, continuous &lt;a href="https://terranovasecurity.com/develop-security-awareness-training/"&gt;security awareness education is paramount&lt;/a&gt;. Conduct regular training sessions to educate your people about the latest threats and minimise the negligent insider threat risk. Utilise realistic phishing simulations to test their preparedness and hone their skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA): &lt;/strong&gt;MFA requires users to provide two or more verification methods to gain access. It&amp;#8217;s an effective way to prevent unauthorised access: even if cybercriminals acquire login credentials, they&amp;#8217;ll be thwarted without the second authentication factor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Regular Backups and Updates: &lt;/strong&gt;Consistent and regular backups ensure that you can recover your data in the event of an attack. Store these backups offline and in multiple locations to protect against potential data loss. Regularly update all systems, software, and applications to patch potential vulnerabilities and stay ahead of threats.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Implement Endpoint Security: &lt;/strong&gt;Endpoint security solutions provide a network-wide defence by monitoring and managing all endpoints. Use advanced &lt;a href="https://www.catonetworks.com/glossary/what-is-endpoint-protection/"&gt;endpoint protection&lt;/a&gt; platforms that employ &lt;a href="https://www.nextdlp.com/resources/blog/machine-learning-in-data-loss-prevention"&gt;machine learning&lt;/a&gt; and behavioural analysis to detect and block malicious activities in real-time, shielding the network from potential breaches.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Establish Clear Communication Protocols: &lt;/strong&gt;Ensure your organization has clear protocols for communication, especially concerning financial transactions or sharing sensitive data. These protocols can prevent BEC and other cyber attack tactics by making it harder for attackers to impersonate trusted entities. Email filtering to detect and quarantine suspicious emails can be an essential ally in this cause.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incident Response and Breach Notification: &lt;/strong&gt;Businesses can react to data breaches efficiently when they have a well-defined incident response plan in place. The impact of data loss incidents is minimized by establishing mechanisms for breach notification, both internally and to impacted parties.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Collaboration and Insights’ Sharing: &lt;/strong&gt;One of the most potent tools in the arsenal against cybercrime is collaboration. By sharing insights, strategies, incident experiences, and lessons learned within the cybersecurity community, businesses can present a united front against these malicious entities. Platforms, forums, and conferences dedicated to cybersecurity provide professionals with a space to share, learn, and evolve.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Humans’ and machines’ collaboration can protect data&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In an ever-evolving cyber landscape, where cybercriminals employ advanced attack techniques against companies’ vulnerabilities, recognising scam patterns is only half the battle. A unified approach to data loss prevention that implements an adequate DLP solution, bundled with continuous awareness training, robust security protocols, and community collaboration, is crucial for ensuring that defences are not only &lt;a href="https://vmblog.com/archive/2023/06/16/striking-a-balance-between-proactive-and-reactive-cybersecurity.aspx"&gt;reactive but proactive&lt;/a&gt; and that a powerful shield is formed against the majority of cyber threats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember, in the world of cybersecurity, complacency is the enemy. Stay informed about scam patterns, stay vigilant, and always be prepared to adapt by adopting adequate DLP solutions to safeguard your critical data and maintain the integrity of your digital assets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/20/recognising-scam-patterns-and-preventing-data-loss-a-unified-approach/"&gt;Recognising Scam Patterns and Preventing Data Loss: A Unified Approach&lt;/a&gt; first appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/20/recognising-scam-patterns-and-preventing-data-loss-a-unified-approach/"&gt;Recognising Scam Patterns and Preventing Data Loss: A Unified Approach&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded>
</item>
<item>
<title>理解英国政府的新网络安全制度，GovAssure</title>
<link>https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/20/understanding-the-uk-governments-new-cybersecurity-regime-govassure/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=understanding-the-uk-governments-new-cybersecurity-regime-govassure</link>
<dc:creator>Guru Writer</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 11:18:29 +0000</pubDate>
<category>Featured</category>
<category>Insight</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.itsecurityguru.org/?p=50430</guid>
<description>&lt;p&gt;With the ever-growing threat of cyberattacks on the UK government and Critical National Infrastructure cyber safety matters more than ever. With the rising tide of ever-resent threat in mind, GovAssure was launched by the UK government in April 2023. It&amp;#8217;s a cyber security programme that aims to ensure government IT systems are fully protected from [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/20/understanding-the-uk-governments-new-cybersecurity-regime-govassure/"&gt;Understanding the UK government’s new cybersecurity regime, GovAssure&lt;/a&gt; first appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/20/understanding-the-uk-governments-new-cybersecurity-regime-govassure/"&gt;Understanding the UK government’s new cybersecurity regime, GovAssure&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
<content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;With the ever-growing threat of cyberattacks on the UK government and Critical National Infrastructure cyber safety matters more than ever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the rising tide of ever-resent threat in mind, GovAssure was launched by the UK government in April 2023. It&amp;#8217;s a cyber security programme that aims to ensure government IT systems are fully protected from cyberattacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new cyber security scheme is run by the Cabinet Office’s Government Security Group (GSG), with input from the National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC). Under this new scheme, all central government departments will have their cyber health reviewed annually through new, more robust criteria.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the launch of the new, more robust scheme, Government Chief Security Officer, Vincent Devine described GovAssure as a chance to gain far greater visibility of the common cyber security challenges facing government, as well as being “a powerful tool for security advocacy”, and it will empower cyber security professionals to strengthen the case for security change and investment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GovAssure aims to review government departments (and select arm’s length bodies’), and approaches to cyber security. It is currently only designated for official systems and does not apply to secret systems or higher.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It will help develop a greater understanding of the cyber security posture and capability of government departments and arm’s length bodies. Through robust annual security audits, departments must now attest to their cyber security assurance measures as set out in the NCSC’s Cyber Assessment Framework (CAF).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CAF sets out indicators of good practice for managing security risk and protecting against cyberattacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The NCSC’s CAF was designed to be used by operators within Critical National Infrastructure (CNI) in relation to the Network &amp;amp; Information Systems (NIS) regulations, which aimed to raise cyber security levels and resilience of key systems across the EU. NIS came into force in the UK in May 2018.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GovAssure replaces existing ‘Departmental Security Health Checks’ that departments must currently provide to the Cabinet Office for review. This is a key part of the Government’s Cyber Security Strategy to improve cyber resilience and help government organisations protect themselves from growing hostile cyber threats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GovAssure is a five-stage process:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organisational contact and services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-scope systems and assignment to the Government CAF profile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CAF self-assessment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Independent assurance review&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Final assessment and targeted improvement plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stage 1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first stage of GovAssure is a scoping exercise. Here, organisations must develop a complete understanding of their strategic context and understand the cyber security threat landscape.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The scope will be defined by the essential services that the department provides, either in relation to CNI, or Operators of Essential Services (OES).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stage 2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once essential services are identified, &lt;em&gt;critical&lt;/em&gt; systems are then identified. These may be a mix of operational and support systems for the identified essential services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are two Government Cyber Assessment Framework (CAF) profiles: Baseline and Enhanced. These profiles will be assigned through discussion with GSG, the NCSC and the Cabinet Office. The enhanced profile will be automatically applied to government CNI.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stage 3&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CAF self-assessment has four objectives: managing security risk, protecting against cyberattacks, detecting cyber security events and minimising the impact of cyber security incidents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Departments should complete the self-assessment with input from relevant key stakeholders within the organisation. The CAF has been mapped to several industry-standard frameworks, including ISO 27001 and NIST SP 800-53.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stage 4&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, accredited third parties will perform independent reviews to verify the department’s self-assessment. This review will assess the level of attainment of the relevant CAF profile, validate the results of self-assessed findings, and determine how effective current cyber security controls are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This assessment will evaluate CAF level attainment, by reviewing the department’s WebCAF submissions, alongside a review of any supporting documents referenced in the submission.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The third-party reviewer will also hold interviews with key stakeholders to review responses on a per objective basis. Reviews will consider the extent to which supporting indicators of good practice have been achieved, partially achieved, or not achieved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stage 5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, once an independent review is completed, a final assessment report is generated and provided to the organisation by the independent assurance provider. GSG will then work with the organisation to develop a targeted improvement plan, outlining a prioritised list of areas for improvement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This process might seem daunting or complex, but many companies can help. AMR CyberSecurity is a GovAssure Independent Assurance Reviewer, for example, which can provide the Stage 4 requirements of GovAssure to relevant organisations. Its highly skilled, qualified assurance consultants can assist organisations in carrying out the Independent Assurance Review, as well as other assurance activities in relation to cyber security.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/20/understanding-the-uk-governments-new-cybersecurity-regime-govassure/"&gt;Understanding the UK government’s new cybersecurity regime, GovAssure&lt;/a&gt; first appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/20/understanding-the-uk-governments-new-cybersecurity-regime-govassure/"&gt;Understanding the UK government’s new cybersecurity regime, GovAssure&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded>
</item>
<item>
<title>bcrypt密码是否能够被破解？</title>
<link>https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/17/can-bcrypt-passwords-be-cracked/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=can-bcrypt-passwords-be-cracked</link>
<dc:creator>Guru Writer</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 14:49:22 +0000</pubDate>
<category>Editor's News</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.itsecurityguru.org/?p=50422</guid>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Specops Software, an Outpost24 company, have released new research about bcrypt-passwords – and how easy (or not) they are to crack. This research follows previously released data on how long it takes attackers to brute force MD5 hashed user passwords with the help of newer hardware. bcrypt is becoming an increasingly popular way to secure passwords, [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/17/can-bcrypt-passwords-be-cracked/"&gt;Can bcrypt Passwords Be Cracked?&lt;/a&gt; first appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/17/can-bcrypt-passwords-be-cracked/"&gt;Can bcrypt Passwords Be Cracked?&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
<content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Specops Software, an Outpost24 company, have &lt;a class="fui-Link ___10kug0w f3rmtva f1ewtqcl fyind8e f1k6fduh f1w7gpdv fk6fouc fjoy568 figsok6 f1hu3pq6 f11qmguv f19f4twv f1tyq0we f1g0x7ka fhxju0i f1qch9an f1cnd47f fqv5qza f1vmzxwi f1o700av f13mvf36 f1cmlufx f9n3di6 f1ids18y f1tx3yz7 f1deo86v f1eh06m1 f1iescvh fhgqx19 f1olyrje f1p93eir f1nev41a f1h8hb77 f1lqvz6u f10aw75t fsle3fq f17ae5zn" title="https://specopssoft.com/blog/hashing-algorithm-cracking-bcrypt-passwords" href="https://specopssoft.com/blog/hashing-algorithm-cracking-bcrypt-passwords" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" aria-label="Link released a blog"&gt;released new research&lt;/a&gt; about bcrypt-passwords – and how easy (or not) they are to crack. This research follows &lt;a class="fui-Link ___10kug0w f3rmtva f1ewtqcl fyind8e f1k6fduh f1w7gpdv fk6fouc fjoy568 figsok6 f1hu3pq6 f11qmguv f19f4twv f1tyq0we f1g0x7ka fhxju0i f1qch9an f1cnd47f fqv5qza f1vmzxwi f1o700av f13mvf36 f1cmlufx f9n3di6 f1ids18y f1tx3yz7 f1deo86v f1eh06m1 f1iescvh fhgqx19 f1olyrje f1p93eir f1nev41a f1h8hb77 f1lqvz6u f10aw75t fsle3fq f17ae5zn" title="https://specopssoft.com/blog/best-password-practices-to-defend-against-modern-cracking-attacks/" href="https://specopssoft.com/blog/best-password-practices-to-defend-against-modern-cracking-attacks/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" aria-label="Link previously released data"&gt;previously released data&lt;/a&gt; on how long it takes attackers to brute force MD5 hashed user passwords with the help of newer hardware.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;bcrypt is becoming an increasingly popular way to secure passwords, as it uses a strong hashing algorithm. Additionally, to increase security, bcrypt also adds a random piece of data to each password hash, ensuring its uniqueness and making it very hard to guess with dictionary or brute force attacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="flex-1 overflow-hidden"&gt;
&lt;div class="react-scroll-to-bottom--css-asxzm-79elbk h-full"&gt;
&lt;div class="react-scroll-to-bottom--css-asxzm-1n7m0yu"&gt;
&lt;div class="flex flex-col text-sm gizmo:pb-9 dark:bg-gray-800 gizmo:dark:bg-transparent"&gt;
&lt;div class="w-full text-token-text-primary border-b border-black/10 gizmo:border-0 dark:border-gray-900/50 gizmo:dark:border-0 bg-gray-50 gizmo:bg-transparent dark:bg-[#444654] gizmo:dark:bg-transparent" data-testid="conversation-turn-3"&gt;
&lt;div class="p-4 gizmo:py-2 justify-center text-base md:gap-6 md:py-6 m-auto"&gt;
&lt;div class="flex flex-1 gap-4 text-base mx-auto md:gap-6 gizmo:gap-3 gizmo:md:px-5 gizmo:lg:px-1 gizmo:xl:px-5 md:max-w-2xl lg:max-w-[38rem] gizmo:md:max-w-3xl gizmo:lg:max-w-[40rem] gizmo:xl:max-w-[48rem] xl:max-w-3xl } group final-completion"&gt;
&lt;div class="relative flex w-[calc(100%-50px)] flex-col gizmo:w-full lg:w-[calc(100%-115px)] agent-turn"&gt;
&lt;div class="flex-col gap-1 md:gap-3"&gt;
&lt;div class="flex flex-grow flex-col max-w-full gap-3 gizmo:gap-0"&gt;
&lt;div class="min-h-[20px] text-message flex flex-col items-start gap-3 whitespace-pre-wrap break-words [.text-message+&amp;amp;]:mt-5 overflow-x-auto" data-message-author-role="assistant" data-message-id="7eea7839-8722-45f3-b1cb-696d079998d4"&gt;
&lt;div class="markdown prose w-full break-words dark:prose-invert light"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bcrypt distinguishes itself from other hashing algorithms by incorporating a &amp;#8216;cost factor.&amp;#8217; This factor indicates the number of password iterations completed prior to hash generation and is appended to the salt. By utilising the cost factor, one can specify the desired number of password iterations and hashing rounds, thereby intensifying the time, effort, and computational resources required to compute the ultimate hash value. This deliberate slowdown significantly impedes the cracking process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research found that a bcrypt hash takes time to make but it also takes time to break. A threat actor might give up, lack the computational power, or it might give security teams the time need to notice suspicious activity. Even with higher computer speeds, bcrypt is very time-consuming to hack via brute force thanks to its variable number of password iterations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, ultimately, bcrypt hashing cannot prevent password compromise altogether. Short, non-complex passwords can still be cracked relatively quickly, highlighting the huge risks of allowing users to create weak (yet very common) passwords. But once a combination of characters are used in passwords over eight characters in length, the time to crack quickly becomes a near-impossible task for hackers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This research coincides with an updated to the Breached Password Protection service. This month, over 21 million compromised passwords were added to the list. Recently, Specops announced a new &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/09/19/specops-software-launches-continuous-scanning-capabilities-for-breached-password-protection/"&gt;continuous scanning capability&lt;/a&gt; for their Breached Password Protection tool.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/17/can-bcrypt-passwords-be-cracked/"&gt;Can bcrypt Passwords Be Cracked?&lt;/a&gt; first appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/17/can-bcrypt-passwords-be-cracked/"&gt;Can bcrypt Passwords Be Cracked?&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded>
</item>
<item>
<title>人工智能的前5个风险</title>
<link>https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/16/top-5-risks-of-artificial-intelligence/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=top-5-risks-of-artificial-intelligence</link>
<dc:creator>Daniel Tannenbaum</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 16:47:39 +0000</pubDate>
<category>Insight</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.itsecurityguru.org/?p=50414</guid>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Artificial intelligence (AI) technology functions in a manner that helps ease human life. Through AI-enabled systems, different industries have been able to minimize human error and automate repetitive processes and tasks while smoothly handling big data. Unlike humans, who are productive only a few hours a day and need time off and breaks for a [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/16/top-5-risks-of-artificial-intelligence/"&gt;Top 5 Risks of Artificial Intelligence&lt;/a&gt; first appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/16/top-5-risks-of-artificial-intelligence/"&gt;Top 5 Risks of Artificial Intelligence&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
<content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/01/13/how-is-ai-technology-going-to-change-business-in-2023/"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Artificial intelligence (AI) technology&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; functions in a manner that helps ease human life. Through AI-enabled systems, different industries have been able to minimize human error and automate repetitive processes and tasks while smoothly handling big data. Unlike humans, who are productive only a few hours a day and need time off and breaks for a healthy work-life balance, AI can operate continuously without breaks, think faster, and handle multiple tasks simultaneously while delivering accurate results.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Despite AI&amp;#8217;s countless benefits, it also comes with some risks that each user should be aware of. Discussed below are the top five risks of artificial intelligence.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;1. Security risks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;While AI technologies continue becoming highly sophisticated, the security concerns linked with their use and the possibility for misuse also rise. Threat actors can leverage the same AI tools meant for human good to commit malicious acts like scams and fraud. As your business increasingly depends on AI for its operations, you should be aware of the security threats you might be exposed to and find ways to safeguard against them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;These&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wiz.io/academy/ai-security"&gt; &lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;AI security&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; risks include data poisoning and manipulation and automated malware. You may also experience impersonation and hallucination abuse. To address AI security challenges, consider:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Prioritizing cybersecurity risk mitigation techniques for AI systems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Strengthening AI system security measures&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Integrating privacy in AI systems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Establishing ethical AI guidelines&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;2. Job loss&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;AI technology has changed how tasks are done, particularly repetitive ones. Although it boosts efficiency, it comes with job loss.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.zippia.com/advice/ai-job-loss-statistics/"&gt; &lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Statistics&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; indicate that 45 million Americans, representing around a quarter of the workforce, risk losing their jobs to AI automation. Worldwide, a billion people might lose their jobs over the next decade due to AI, with 375 million jobs being at obsolescence risk from AI automation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;3. Privacy concerns&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;AI systems usually collect data from every corner of the web, including personal data, to train AI models or personalize customer experiences. Also, AI flourishes on data, meaning the more data it has, the better it’ll learn and perform. However, this creates a significant privacy concern. When people use AI, it keeps information about them and their chat history.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;The huge amounts of data AI gathers and processes may have sensitive information. When this data isn’t adequately safeguarded, it could be a ready target for hackers or cybercriminals, resulting in spear phishing attacks and&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/07/04/breaking-it-down-what-you-need-to-know-about-data-breaches/"&gt; &lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;data breaches&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;. As such, you should avoid typing sensitive or personal information when using AI to prevent privacy concerns.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;4. AI over-dependence&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;While AI makes human life easier, it comes at the cost of reducing their critical thinking capabilities. Easy tasks that once called for problem-solving skills are now outsourced to AI-based systems and tools. The ease and efficiency AI brings erodes critical thinking skills and creativity because people become too dependent on this technology for decision-making and information. This turns them into passive data consumers, which can lead to the spread of fake news or misinformation. As such, you should balance human input and AI to preserve cognitive abilities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;5. Ethical dilemmas&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;The rising use of AI has resulted in multiple&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://research.aimultiple.com/ai-ethics/"&gt; &lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;ethical dilemmas&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;. One of the most significant issues is AI&amp;#8217;s use in applications that require ethical or moral judgment. For instance, although AI can assist doctors and enhance diagnoses, the machine can make a mistake that hurts a patient. Such issues require the establishment of regulatory frameworks that ascertain responsible, ethical AI use.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Endnote&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;While AI comes with many benefits, it also has some associated threats. Familiarize yourself with the top AI risks and how to safeguard against them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/16/top-5-risks-of-artificial-intelligence/"&gt;Top 5 Risks of Artificial Intelligence&lt;/a&gt; first appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/16/top-5-risks-of-artificial-intelligence/"&gt;Top 5 Risks of Artificial Intelligence&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded>
</item>
<item>
<title>Centripetal与爱尔兰文艺复兴合作伙伴扩大渠道计划</title>
<link>https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/16/centripetal-expands-channel-program-with-irish-renaissance-partnership/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=centripetal-expands-channel-program-with-irish-renaissance-partnership</link>
<dc:creator>Guru Writer</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 13:59:39 +0000</pubDate>
<category>Channel News</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.itsecurityguru.org/?p=50408</guid>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Today, intelligence-powered cybersecurity pros Centripetal have announced a strategic partnership with Renaissance, the leading Irish value-added distributor in Ireland. This collaboration marks a significant milestone in bolstering Ireland&amp;#8217;s cybersecurity landscape and underscores the commitment to combating the rising tide of cyber threats. Additionally, this partnership bolsters Centripetal&amp;#8217;s channel presence. The cost and complexity of protecting [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/16/centripetal-expands-channel-program-with-irish-renaissance-partnership/"&gt;Centripetal Expands Channel Program With Irish Renaissance Partnership&lt;/a&gt; first appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/16/centripetal-expands-channel-program-with-irish-renaissance-partnership/"&gt;Centripetal Expands Channel Program With Irish Renaissance Partnership&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
<content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Today, intelligence-powered cybersecurity pros &lt;a href="https://hubs.la/Q01R9LG50"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Centripetal&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; have &lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;announced a strategic partnership with Renaissance, the leading Irish value-added distributor in Ireland. This collaboration marks a significant milestone in bolstering Ireland&amp;#8217;s cybersecurity landscape and underscores the commitment to combating the rising tide of cyber threats. Additionally, this partnership bolsters Centripetal&amp;#8217;s channel presence.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;The cost and complexity of protecting IT assets from cyberthreats is increasing and enterprises are struggling to know where best to invest their efforts and budgets for maximum impact. Centripetal’s CleanINTERNET® delivers real-time protection against all known cyber attacks by operationalising the world&amp;#8217;s largest collection of threat intelligence, in real-time. The solution also provides a team of elite, highly skilled, intelligence operational analysts augmented by AI technology to monitor and protect an organization&amp;#8217;s network. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&amp;#8220;In an age where the digital terrain is rife with escalating cyber threats, Centripetal stands as a crucial ally for Irish organizations in pursuit of thorough protection,” said Michael Conway, Director at Renaissance. “This partnership signifies a transformation in the cybersecurity landscape of Ireland. CleanINTERNET® not only delivers a robust alternative protection strategy but does so at a dramatically lower cost, redefining the landscape of digital defense.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;With this partnership, Centripetal and Renaissance aim to empower Irish organisations to stay ahead of cyber threats, reinforcing the importance of intelligence-powered cybersecurity in an era where traditional, legacy, methods fall short. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;“This collaboration marks a significant milestone, extending the reach of proactive, intelligence-powered cybersecurity solutions to organizations across Ireland,” added Dave Silke, European MD at Centripetal. “Together, we are excited to elevate the standards of digital defense in the Irish market.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, Centripetal announced their physical expansion into Ireland by opening a Galway office, the European Cyber Intelligence Centre of Excellence. This happened at the same time as their &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/05/30/centripetal-extends-innovative-cleaninternet-technology-to-the-cloud/"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;CleanINTERNET® technology expanded to the Cloud.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/16/centripetal-expands-channel-program-with-irish-renaissance-partnership/"&gt;Centripetal Expands Channel Program With Irish Renaissance Partnership&lt;/a&gt; first appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/16/centripetal-expands-channel-program-with-irish-renaissance-partnership/"&gt;Centripetal Expands Channel Program With Irish Renaissance Partnership&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded>
</item>
<item>
<title>SoSafe以个性化方法开创了对意识培训的先驱。</title>
<link>https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/16/sosafe-pioneers-personalised-approach-to-awareness-training/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sosafe-pioneers-personalised-approach-to-awareness-training</link>
<dc:creator>Guru Writer</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 12:18:42 +0000</pubDate>
<category>News</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.itsecurityguru.org/?p=50405</guid>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Security awareness and training company SoSafe has announced the launch of the next-generation of personalised learning. The news was revealed at their Human Firewall Conference earlier this week. This latest innovation aims to make secure behaviour second nature for humans.  SoSafe’s personalisation engine multiplies the learning effect while saving up to 30% of time investment [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/16/sosafe-pioneers-personalised-approach-to-awareness-training/"&gt;SoSafe Pioneers Personalised Approach to Awareness Training&lt;/a&gt; first appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/16/sosafe-pioneers-personalised-approach-to-awareness-training/"&gt;SoSafe Pioneers Personalised Approach to Awareness Training&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
<content:encoded>&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Security awareness and training company &lt;a href="https://sosafe-awareness.com/ppc/security-awareness-training-product-demo/?utm_term=sosafe&amp;amp;utm_campaign=UKI_EN_SoSafe-Brand_Q12023&amp;amp;utm_source=bing&amp;amp;utm_medium=paid&amp;amp;hsa_acc=2315609737&amp;amp;hsa_cam=19530241617&amp;amp;hsa_grp=1159986601813877&amp;amp;hsa_ad=&amp;amp;hsa_src=o&amp;amp;hsa_tgt=kwd-72499853886825:loc-188&amp;amp;hsa_kw=sosafe&amp;amp;hsa_mt=e&amp;amp;hsa_net=adwords&amp;amp;hsa_ver=3&amp;amp;msclkid=05ac29b9bfda17839aa84cec45e92105&amp;amp;utm_content=SoSafe%20brand"&gt;SoSafe&lt;/a&gt; has announced the launch of the next-generation of personalised learning. The news was revealed at their &lt;a href="https://humanfirewallconference.com/"&gt;Human Firewall Conference&lt;/a&gt; earlier this week. This latest innovation aims to make secure behaviour second nature for humans.  SoSafe’s personalisation engine multiplies the learning effect while saving up to 30% of time investment of employees.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Users are set to benefit from a data-driven individualised learning journey, receiving targeted content that addresses their unique risk profiles, to ensure a deeper understanding and engagement with cybersecurity concepts.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;A personalised approach to cybersecurity awareness training may be a refreshing alternative to standardised training, considering that awareness training remains a significant challenge for management teams across all industries. However, it&amp;#8217;s vitally important, especially as&lt;a href="https://www.cybsafe.com/"&gt; research shows&lt;/a&gt; that human error is a leading factor of breaches. For many organisations, it can be hard to identify what training needs to be delivered, who needs to be trained, and how people can be engaged best.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Dr. Niklas Hellemann, Psychologist and CEO at SoSafe noted: “Psychological research underscores the unmatched potential of personalised learning for lasting learning success and behavioural transformation. We’ve always had this vision of personalised, adaptive learning at the core of our product – what we are releasing today is the first step in what we believe will be a revolution in the world of security awareness and corporate training in general. With this, we follow our goal to build strong &amp;#8216;security instincts&amp;#8217; so that making secure decisions becomes second nature to everyone. It is a comprehensive and deep process of changing individuals&amp;#8217; knowledge, skills, and attitudes regarding cybersecurity.”&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;SoSafe’s training begins with a comprehensive initial survey, capturing data on user work habits, equipment, and working environment. In addition, SoSafe announces upcoming integrations with leading Human Resources Information Systems, including Workday, SAP, and Personio, significantly bolsters the data foundation for personalised learning.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;This insight-driven approach ensures content delivery through a personalised learning engine tailored to each user&amp;#8217;s unique risk profile with a steadfast goal: Bridging the knowledge gap promptly, internalising secure behaviour and maintaining consistent learning levels using only essential content across SoSafe’s multi-channel awareness platform. Additionally, a redesigned learning interface offers a streamlined yet engaging user experience, guiding learners to their next lessons without visual clutter.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Goncalo Gaiolas, CPO at SoSafe: “IT Security leaders are struggling because corporate training can be resource-intense, often without firm proof of success. They are under pressure to be compliant with increased regulations while employees are not motivated to do existing training. We are committed to changing this: SoSafe is the only cyber security awareness platform that offers full user personalisation, enabling us to empower employees to have strong security instincts at two times the speed of regular security awareness training. And this is only the beginning. Further releases are planned soon, that embed personalised learning more and more at the core of our product.”&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Alternative approaches to cybersecurity awareness training have long been a topic of conversation for cybersecurity professionals. As organisation&amp;#8217;s strive for innovative approaches to training (&lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/03/29/back-and-bigger-than-ever-the-inside-man-season-5-takes-a-stab-at-power-hungry-adversaries/"&gt;KnowBe4&amp;#8217;s Inside Man big-budget web series,&lt;/a&gt; for example), it&amp;#8217;s evidently more vital than ever that leaders sit up to the idea of revolutionising awareness given the increased sophistication of threats.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/16/sosafe-pioneers-personalised-approach-to-awareness-training/"&gt;SoSafe Pioneers Personalised Approach to Awareness Training&lt;/a&gt; first appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/16/sosafe-pioneers-personalised-approach-to-awareness-training/"&gt;SoSafe Pioneers Personalised Approach to Awareness Training&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded>
</item>
<item>
<title>新的Synopsys研究表明软件漏洞数量下降</title>
<link>https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/14/new-synopsys-research-reveals-a-decrease-in-software-vulnerabilities/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=new-synopsys-research-reveals-a-decrease-in-software-vulnerabilities</link>
<dc:creator>The Gurus</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 15:28:39 +0000</pubDate>
<category>Featured</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.itsecurityguru.org/?p=50393</guid>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Today, Synopsys has released its 2023 Software Vulnerability Snapshot report, showcasing a notable decline in vulnerabilities within target applications. The Synopsys Cybersecurity Research Center (CyRC) analysed the data, revealing a decrease from 97% in 2020 to 83% in 2022. This positive trend suggests that practices such as code reviews, automated testing, and continuous integration are [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/14/new-synopsys-research-reveals-a-decrease-in-software-vulnerabilities/"&gt;New Synopsys Research Reveals a Decrease in Software Vulnerabilities&lt;/a&gt; first appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/14/new-synopsys-research-reveals-a-decrease-in-software-vulnerabilities/"&gt;New Synopsys Research Reveals a Decrease in Software Vulnerabilities&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
<content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Today, Synopsys has released its &lt;a href="https://www.synopsys.com/software-integrity/resources/analyst-reports/software-vulnerability-trends.html?cmp=pr-sig&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral"&gt;2023 Software Vulnerability Snapshot report&lt;/a&gt;, showcasing a notable decline in vulnerabilities within target applications. The &lt;a href="https://www.synopsys.com/software-integrity/cybersecurity-research-center.html?cmp=pr-sig&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral"&gt;Synopsys Cybersecurity Research Center (CyRC)&lt;/a&gt; analysed the data, revealing a decrease from 97% in 2020 to 83% in 2022. This positive trend suggests that practices such as code reviews, automated testing, and continuous integration are effectively reducing common programming errors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The report spans three years of data (2020 &amp;#8211; 2022) obtained from tests conducted by Synopsys Security Testing Services. These tests targeted web applications, mobile applications, network systems, and source code, employing various security testing techniques like penetration testing, dynamic application security testing (DAST), mobile application security testing (MAST), and network security testing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the industry celebrates this progress, the data underscores the inadequacy of relying solely on a single security testing solution, such as static application security testing (SAST). Notably, server misconfigurations accounted for an average of 18% of total vulnerabilities discovered over the three-year testing period. The report emphasizes the importance of a multi-layered security approach, combining SAST to identify coding flaws, DAST to assess running applications, SCA to pinpoint vulnerabilities from third-party components, and penetration testing to catch issues overlooked during internal testing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jason Schmitt, the general manager of the Synopsys Software Integrity Group, commented on the significance of the decrease in known vulnerabilities, stating, “For the first time in years, we’re seeing a decrease in the number of known vulnerabilities in software, which provides new hope that organisations are taking security seriously and prioritising a strategic and holistic approach to software security in order to make a lasting impact.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Key findings from the report include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High-severity vulnerabilities are less prevalent, with only 27% of tests revealing high-severity vulnerabilities and 6.2% containing critical-severity vulnerabilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Information leakage remains a top security risk, constituting an average of 19% of total vulnerabilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cross-site scripting vulnerabilities are on the rise, accounting for 19% of high-risk vulnerabilities in 2022.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Third-party software poses increased risks, with 25% of tests uncovering vulnerabilities in third-party libraries among the top 10 security issues in 2022.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To delve deeper into the findings, interested parties can download the &lt;a href="https://www.synopsys.com/software-integrity/resources/analyst-reports/software-vulnerability-trends.html?cmp=pr-sig&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral"&gt;2023 Software Vulnerability Snapshot: A Three-Year Analysis of the 10 Most Common Web and Software Application Vulnerabilities&lt;/a&gt; or read the detailed &lt;a href="https://www.synopsys.com/blogs/software-security/software-vulnerability-snapshot-report-findings.html?cmp=pr-sig&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral"&gt;blog post&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/14/new-synopsys-research-reveals-a-decrease-in-software-vulnerabilities/"&gt;New Synopsys Research Reveals a Decrease in Software Vulnerabilities&lt;/a&gt; first appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org/2023/11/14/new-synopsys-research-reveals-a-decrease-in-software-vulnerabilities/"&gt;New Synopsys Research Reveals a Decrease in Software Vulnerabilities&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://www.itsecurityguru.org"&gt;IT Security Guru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>