<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<id>https://techplanet.today/feed</id>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/feed" rel="self"/>
<title>TechPlanet</title>
<subtitle/>
<updated>2023-11-20T14:57:53+00:00</updated>
<entry>
<title>哪个更好，Asus Tuf F15 还是 A15？哪一个更耗电？</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/which-is-better-the-asus-tuf-f15-or-a15-which-one-drains-more-battery" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2229638</id>
<author>
<name>laptopoutlet</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                Are you looking for the ultimate gaming companion: the Asus TUF F15 or A15? Which one delivers peak performance, and which one leaves you reaching for the charger?&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
When it comes to gaming laptops, the choice between the Asus TUF F15 and A15 can be challenging, as both models have their own set of unique features and specifications to offer. Gamers often seek a balance between performance, portability, and battery life.&lt;br /&gt;
Battery life is a critical consideration for anyone looking to invest in a gaming laptop, as uninterrupted gaming sessions are highly dependent on it.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
This blog will provide a comprehensive comparison of the Asus F15 and A15 and their key attributes so you can make an informed decision about investing in your next gaming powerhouse.&lt;br /&gt;
So, let&amp;rsquo;s get into it!&lt;br /&gt;
ASUS TUF F15 Vs A15: Detailed Comparison&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
Here's a detailed comparison of the performance and battery life of both laptops. Let's begin by examining the specificati...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-11-20T14:57:53+00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>如何提高您的Magento应用速度？</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/how-to-increase-your-magento-application-speed" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2228527</id>
<author>
<name>Pooja Naik</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                Understanding the Magento application and its challenges&lt;br /&gt;
The&amp;nbsp;Magento application&amp;nbsp;is a popular e-commerce platform that provides businesses with a robust and scalable solution for their online stores. However, one of the common challenges faced by Magento users is the slow speed of their applications. This can have a significant impact on the user experience, resulting in decreased customer satisfaction and lower conversion rates.&lt;br /&gt;
BigCloudy offers&amp;nbsp;best optimized and caching hosting services&amp;nbsp;and prioritizes delivering an exceptional hosting experience tailored specifically for Magento websites, ensuring optimal speed, reliability, and overall performance for online businesses built on this powerful e-commerce platform.&lt;br /&gt;
There are several factors that contribute to the slow speed of Magento applications. One of the main reasons is the complex and resource-intensive nature of the platform. Magento is built on a powerful infrastructure that offers a wide range of featu...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-11-18T12:13:15+00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>在社交媒体上打造强大的个人品牌。</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/creating-a-powerful-personal-brand-on-social-media" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2224926</id>
<author>
<name>Mark Halland</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                In today's digital age, personal branding on social media has become a pivotal element of success, both personally and professionally. With billions of users worldwide, platforms like Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, LinkedIn, and TikTok offer immense opportunities for individuals to create and nurture a strong personal brand. In this comprehensive guide, we will explore the strategies and techniques needed to build a robust personal brand on social media, incorporating statistics and real-life examples to illustrate our points.&lt;br /&gt;
The Importance of a Personal Brand on Social Media&lt;br /&gt;
Career Advancement:&lt;br /&gt;
A robust personal brand on social media can significantly impact your career opportunities. In today's digital world, potential employers, clients, and business partners are likely to research you online before making decisions. Your online presence can make you a more attractive candidate or partner. According to a CareerBuilder survey, 70% of employers use social media to screen job candid...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-11-13T13:18:57+00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>Excel作为电子竞技的崛起</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/the-rise-of-excel-as-an-esport" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2224587</id>
<author>
<name>Kelly</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                It's fair to say most of us don't like spreadsheets, but the people who do like them, like them a lot. And while many of us use Microsoft Excel in our day-to-day work, an elite few have adapted the world's most popular spreadsheet software into an eSports phenomenon.&lt;br /&gt;
The Excel World Championship&lt;br /&gt;
In 2022, the Excel World Championship debuted as part of ESPN's The Ocho, an annual showcase of lower-profile sports like axe throwing, corgi racing, and, of course, the slippery stair climb. The vast majority of viewers had never even conceived of competitive Excel before, as there are some levels of nerdy that are simply beyond mere mortal ken.&lt;br /&gt;
The sport gained unexpected popularity, leading to its renewal for the 2023 Ocho. The championship is set to hold its finale in the Las Vegas HyperX eSports Arena this December, featuring a prize pool of $10,000 across the competition.&lt;br /&gt;
Origins of Competitive Excel&lt;br /&gt;
Excel as an eSport didn't appear out of nowhere fully formed in 2022. It emerged from an...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-11-12T18:27:00+00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>全球沙资源短缺：一个紧迫问题</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/the-global-sand-shortage-a-critical-issue" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2224586</id>
<author>
<name>Jacob Enderson</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                Introduction&lt;br /&gt;
The idea of running out of sand might seem absurd considering the vast deserts covering our planet. However, the reality is more nuanced, and the global demand for sand is reaching unprecedented levels. In this article, we'll delve into the surprising reasons behind the impending sand shortage and explore potential solutions.&lt;br /&gt;
The Extent of the Issue&lt;br /&gt;
While deserts indeed contain abundant sand, not all sand is created equal. Silicon, a crucial component of silica sand, constitutes 27.7% of the Earth's crust. This resource is extensively used, with over 50 billion tons of sand and gravel consumed annually in various industries such as construction, electronics, and manufacturing.&lt;br /&gt;
Sand Composition Matters&lt;br /&gt;
Sand is a result of the gradual erosion of rocks over thousands of years, making it a technically renewable resource. However, the properties of sand vary based on its origin. Concrete, for instance, requires water-weathered sand due to its rough and angular grains, providing...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-11-12T18:23:00+00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>GraphQL或REST：选择正确的API</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/graphql-or-rest-choosing-the-right-api" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2224013</id>
<author>
<name>Ovais Naseem</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                A little bit of background&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
It all began in the early days of computing when computers were massive, standalone machines. Communication was limited, so there was no need for standardized interfaces yet. The computers were primarily used in isolated environments for specific scientific, engineering, or business applications.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
It was only as technology advanced and networks were established that they became more interconnected, and communication between them became more practical. As a result, there was a need for a common language to communicate effectively, making way for the first APIs. These early APIs, although mostly proprietary and limited to specific hardware or software systems, were in the form of libraries and protocols. This means that the developers could access certain functionalities or services either by using pre-written code libraries or by following specific communication protocols.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
The current state of APIs&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
Today, the concept of APIs expands...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-11-10T11:58:02+00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>顶级建议：如何照顾孩子，避免过度使用电子设备

在现代社会中，电子设备在孩子们的生活中扮演着越来越重要的角色。然而，如果不加以控制，过度使用电子设备对孩子们的健康和幸福可能会产生负面影响。以下是一些建议，帮助父母们照顾好孩子们，避免过度使用电子设备。

1. 设定规定的屏幕时间：为孩子们设置每天可以使用电子设备的时间限制。可以根据孩子们的年龄和需求来制定合理的规定。

2. 鼓励户外活动：鼓励孩子们参与户外运动和游戏，使他们获得更多的运动和新鲜空气。

3. 亲子互动时间：为了减少孩子们对电子设备的依赖，家庭中应该创造出一些亲子互动的时刻，例如做饭、画画、读书等。

4. 提供其他娱乐选择：为孩子们提供其他娱乐选择，如玩具、益智游戏、乐器等，以帮助他们发展兴趣和才能。

5. 设置不使用电子设备的区域和时间：为了促进孩子们的学习和交流能力，家里应该确立一些不使用电子设备的区域和时间。

6. 做出互联网安全教育：教导孩子们如何使用电子设备和互联网的安全知识，避免沉迷虚拟世界，同时保护个人隐私。

7. 以身作则：家长应该是良好行为的榜样，容易上瘾的行为也会影响孩子们。要自觉减少自己对电子设备的使用，以示好的示范。

8. 定期检查设备的使用情况：家长应该定期检查孩子们使用电子设备的情况，确保他们在健康和适当的范围内使用。

通过采取这些措施，家长们可以更好地照顾孩子们，避免他们过度依赖电子设备，从而促进他们的全面发展。</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/top-tips-to-take-care-of-childrens-from-gadget-use" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2223291</id>
<author>
<name>Shariful Islam</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                In today's digital age, children are growing up surrounded by gadgets and screens. While technology offers countless benefits, excessive gadget use can pose risks to children's physical and mental well-being. As parents and caregivers, it is crucial to navigate the digital landscape mindfully, setting appropriate boundaries and fostering healthy habits.&lt;br /&gt;
This article provides valuable insights and practical tips on how to protect your children from the negative effects of excessive gadget use.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
1. Understand the Risks of Excessive Gadget Use&lt;br /&gt;
The proliferation of gadgets has brought about various risks for children:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Physical Health Issues: Prolonged screen time can lead to issues like eyestrain, poor posture, and disrupted sleep patterns.&lt;br /&gt;
Mental Health Concerns: Excessive gadget use has been linked to increased stress, anxiety, and even depression among children.&lt;br /&gt;
Social Impact: Spending too much time online might hinder the development of essential social skills and face-to-face...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-11-09T11:51:56+00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>14个令人信服的原因，解释了为何WordPress继续统治无朕</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/14-compelling-reasons-why-wordpress-continues-to-reign-supreme" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2221788</id>
<author>
<name>4GoodHosting</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                Businesses are constantly seeking methods to gain a competitive edge online. Selecting the optimal website development platform is crucial for the success of small businesses operating with limited budgets.&lt;br /&gt;
Despite the emergence of numerous alternatives over the years, WordPress continues to maintain its popularity as a preferred choice for small businesses aiming to establish a robust online presence.&lt;br /&gt;
This article delves into the factors that make WordPress a favoured option among small business owners in 2023.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
WordPress is scalable and reasonably priced&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
WordPress's cost-effectiveness stands out as a key factor in its dominance of the SMEs market. It's accessible to anyone as the core software can be downloaded, installed, and customized without the need for a licensing fee, thanks to its open-source nature.&lt;br /&gt;
Moreover, for those seeking advanced functionality, there is a wide range of premium options available alongside free themes and plugins. This scalable and budget-fri...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-11-07T15:59:38+00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>如何仅通过频道名称找到YouTube的ID</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/how-to-find-youtube-id-with-just-channel-name" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2221680</id>
<author>
<name>Tuhina Rastogi</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
YouTube channel IDs are unique identifiers for YouTube channels. They are used in a variety of ways, such as to embed videos on other websites, to access channel analytics, and to use the YouTube API.&lt;br /&gt;
While YouTube channel IDs are public information, they can be difficult to find. This is because YouTube recently removed channel IDs from channel URLs and replaced them with handles.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
How to Find YouTube ID&lt;br /&gt;
However, there are still a few ways to find YouTube channel IDs, even if you only know the channel name.&lt;br /&gt;
Method 1: Using the YouTube API&lt;br /&gt;
The YouTube API is a powerful tool that can be used to access a variety of YouTube data, including channel IDs.&lt;br /&gt;
To use the YouTube API to find a channel ID, you will need to create a Google Cloud Platform project and enable the YouTube Data API v3.&lt;br /&gt;
Once you have enabled the API, you can use the following code to find the channel ID for any channel name:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Python&lt;br /&gt;
import io&lt;br /&gt;
import json&lt;br /&gt;
import requests&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
API_KEY = "YOUR_API_KE...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-11-07T12:45:21+00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>在公有云、私有云和混合云解决方案之间进行选择</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/choosing-between-public-private-and-hybrid-cloud-solutions" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2221604</id>
<author>
<name>Jinal Prajapati</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                Being a business owner, you're passionate about your company, and you're determined to see it succeed. To be a successful business owner, you must change your IT infrastructure. But when your current system needs to be updated and can't meet the needs of your expanding business. It needs a solution that is scalable, cost-effective, and protected. You've heard about cloud computing, but you must determine if the solution is right.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Public, private, and hybrid cloud solutions have benefits and drawbacks. We'll assist you in selecting the best cloud solution for your business requirements in this blog article.&lt;br /&gt;
The public cloud is the considerable standard type of cloud computing. It's offered by large providers like AWS, Azure, and Google Cloud Platform. Public cloud is a good option for businesses that need a scalable and cost-effective solution.&lt;br /&gt;
A private cloud is a dedicated cloud environment for your business. Private clouds offer more control and security than public clouds,...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-11-07T11:47:00+00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>稳定币开发的最佳区块链平台</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/best-blockchain-platforms-for-stablecoin-development" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2221595</id>
<author>
<name>Oodles Blockchain</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                Stablecoins have become a pivotal element within the cryptocurrency development ecosystem, combining the reliability of conventional fiat currencies with the efficiency and security of blockchain technology. These digital assets, supported by a leading cryptocurrency development company, have garnered widespread acceptance across diverse applications, encompassing trading, cross-border remittances, and serving as a dependable store of value. If you’re contemplating venturing into the realm of stablecoin development, the selection of an appropriate blockchain platform holds the utmost importance. In this article, we will delve into a selection of the finest blockchain platforms tailored for stablecoin development, each possessing its distinct features and merits.&lt;br /&gt;
Best Blockchain Platforms for Stablecoin Development&lt;br /&gt;
Ethereum&lt;br /&gt;
Ethereum is a leading smart contract platform for stablecoin development. IIt is a great choice for creating stablecoins like Tether (USDT), USD Coin (USDC), and...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-11-07T11:39:02+00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>您是一位Android开发者吗？以下是您需要了解的！</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/are-you-an-android-developer-heres-what-you-need-to-know" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2221487</id>
<author>
<name>kim jes</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                An Android developer is responsible for creating software applications that run on smartphones and tablets. They make sure that apps are responsive and take the minimum time to open.&lt;br /&gt;
Android developers also need to be proficient in Java, the programming language that underlies the Android platform. They should also know how to use a version control system like Git, which helps them keep track of changes and provide access to earlier versions of their code.&lt;br /&gt;
1. Java&lt;br /&gt;
As the world&amp;rsquo;s most popular mobile operating system, Android has created a huge demand for developers. Because of its open-source nature, it is easier to get started in this field than other platforms, making it a great choice for developers with different backgrounds.&lt;br /&gt;
Developing apps for Android requires an understanding of Java, the most popular programming language. It is a general-purpose language that allows you to create programs and applications that work across multiple hardware and software systems. It has...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-11-07T10:37:51+00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>关于如何在Solana区块链上开发反对DApp的指南</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/a-guide-to-counter-dapp-development-on-solana-blockchain" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2220756</id>
<author>
<name>Oodles Blockchain</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                This blog gives a comprehensive guide to&amp;nbsp;smart contract development&amp;nbsp;using Anchor for counter dApp development on the Solana blockchain.&lt;br /&gt;
About Solana&lt;br /&gt;
Solana is a high-performance blockchain known for its remarkable speed and scalability. It uses proof-of-history (PoH) and proof-of-stake (PoS) to process thousands of transactions per second, offering low fees. Solana&amp;rsquo;s native cryptocurrency is SOL.&lt;br /&gt;
Its expanding environment fosters the growth of decentralised apps, or dApps. The network's primary goals are interoperability and decentralisation. Solana is a strong blockchain innovation platform in spite of a few challenges.&lt;br /&gt;
Check It Out:&amp;nbsp;What Makes Solana Blockchain Development Stand Out&lt;br /&gt;
Writing Smart Contracts on Solana using Anchor&lt;br /&gt;
Set Up Environment&lt;br /&gt;
Install Rust, Solana CLI, and Anchor CLI for development, for more details refer to&amp;nbsp;https://www.anchor-lang.com/docs/installation.&lt;br /&gt;
Initialize Project&lt;br /&gt;
Use Anchor CLI to create a project with smart contract...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-11-06T12:54:31+00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>切换到娱乐模式：任天堂Switch评测</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/switching-to-fun-a-nintendo-switch-review" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2219942</id>
<author>
<name>Onetechspot02</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                &lt;br /&gt;
Title: **Switching to Fun: A Nintendo Switch Review**&lt;br /&gt;
The world of gaming has evolved significantly over the years, from the simple pleasures of Pong to the immersive experiences of virtual reality. Amidst this ever-changing landscape, one gaming console has managed to capture the hearts of millions: the Nintendo Switch. Released in 2017, the Nintendo Switch quickly gained a reputation for its versatility, innovative design, and an impressive library of games. In this review, we'll dive into what makes the Nintendo Switch a unique and enjoyable gaming platform.&lt;br /&gt;
**Hardware and Design: A Stroke of Genius**&lt;br /&gt;
The first thing that strikes you about the Nintendo Switch is its ingenious design. The console itself is a tablet-like device with a 6.2-inch touchscreen, making it easily portable and allowing you to take your gaming on the go. The Switch can be used in three different modes: handheld mode, tabletop mode, and TV mode. The transition between these modes is seamless and takes only...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-11-04T19:53:14+00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>如何从Snap地图上下载视频？</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/how-to-download-videos-from-the-snap-map" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2219493</id>
<author>
<name>Salmen2</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                Snapchat is a widely popular social messaging app that empowers users to send brief videos to friends, viewable for a limited time. Beyond personal exchanges, it offers a platform for sharing videos with a global audience through Spotlight and Snap Map, allowing anyone around the world to access these short videos. While saving your favourite videos from Spotlight is a seamless process, downloading videos from Snap Map can be a bit tricky. Thankfully, SocieTools, the latest tool in the market, provides a simple solution to this challenge.&lt;br /&gt;
What is Snapchat?&lt;br /&gt;
Snapchat is a dynamic social messaging app that offers users the ability to share short videos or images in two distinct ways: through their stories or by sending them directly to friends. However, the unique aspect of Snapchat lies in the temporary nature of these posts. Let's delve into the time limits associated with each feature:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Stories: These posts are available for a maximum of 24 hours, providing a day-long glimpse into the...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-11-03T21:20:34+00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>使用Linux/Unix中的TRAP命令及示例</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/using-the-trap-command-in-linuxunix-with-examples" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2219427</id>
<author>
<name>Den W.</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                Managing processes in the Linux operating system can be a challenging task, but Linux provides powerful tools to simplify and enhance the process. One such useful tool is the trap command. In this article, we'll explore what the trap command does and how to use it with practical examples.&lt;br /&gt;
What is the trap Command?&lt;br /&gt;
The trap command is used to handle signals that can be sent to a process. Signals are a way for other processes or the system to notify a process of specific events or states. For instance, a signal can be sent to a process to request it to terminate or restart.&lt;br /&gt;
The trap command allows us to define actions that should be taken when a process receives a specific signal. Possible actions include executing certain commands, ignoring the signal, or even terminating the process.&lt;br /&gt;
trap Command Syntax&lt;br /&gt;
The syntax of the trap command is as follows:&lt;br /&gt;
trap 'command' SIGNAL&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
'command' - the command or list of commands to execute when the SIGNAL is received.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
SIGNAL - the name of the sign...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-11-03T15:46:00+00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>使用Laravel在所有视图中分享数据的4个技巧</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/4-techniques-for-sharing-data-across-all-views-in-laravel" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2219424</id>
<author>
<name>Den W.</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                In this article, we will explore four methods to efficiently share common variables or data across all views in Laravel, eliminating the need to manually pass them to each view. This becomes particularly useful when you have data like navigation menu items or global variables that you want to access in multiple views.&lt;br /&gt;
To achieve this, you can employ the following approaches:&lt;br /&gt;
Method 1: Utilizing AppServiceProvider&lt;br /&gt;
In your Laravel project, navigate to app/Providers/AppServiceProvider.php and insert the following code snippet:&lt;br /&gt;
namespace App\Providers;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
use Illuminate\Support\Facades\View;&lt;br /&gt;
use Illuminate\Support\ServiceProvider;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
class AppServiceProvider extends ServiceProvider&lt;br /&gt;
{&lt;br /&gt;
    public function boot(): void&lt;br /&gt;
    {&lt;br /&gt;
        View::share('myGlobalKey', 'This is our value');&lt;br /&gt;
    }&lt;br /&gt;
}&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Replace 'myGlobalKey' with your desired key name and 'This is our value' with the actual value or data you intend to share. Create a test.blade.php file and include the following code:&lt;br /&gt;
Test: {{ $myGlobalKey }}...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-11-03T15:41:00+00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>神经网络算法的类型</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/types-of-neural-network-algorithms" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2219274</id>
<author>
<name>Lubna Mobeen</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
Neural networks are the fundamental components of deep learning techniques, and these are the most important topics in this field. Deep learning is a sub-branch of machine learning, and it deals with the training of the machine without any coding or supervision. In this article, we will discuss the basic types of neural network algorithms in deep learning and understand how they work. There are multiple types of neural network algorithms, and we will try to cover the most common types that all students must know.&lt;br /&gt;
Introduction to Neural Network&lt;br /&gt;
The neural networks are inspired by the workings of human brains, where the neurons are distributed in a specific pattern and transfer and process information from one part of the brain to the other. A neural network has three types of layers:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Input layer&lt;br /&gt;
Output layer&lt;br /&gt;
Hidden layer&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The number of hidden layers is important because they determine the complexity and performance of the neural network. The weights are assigned to th...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-11-03T12:00:11+00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>避免在2023年犯的7个常见网页设计错误</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/7-common-web-design-mistakes-you-should-avoid-in-2023-1" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2218731</id>
<author>
<name>Ryder Jaxon</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                Before Talking Straight About&amp;nbsp;Web Design Mistakes,&amp;nbsp;Let&amp;rsquo;s Understand The Importance Of Design.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
Websites are the digital depiction of your business. So, they demonstrate the business&amp;rsquo; products and level of services you deliver and how well you meet your client&amp;rsquo;s needs. That means customers will trust what your website will tell them. What if your website is yet to be able to fulfil its job smoothly? For example, it might have some flaws in the design, content, or usability that eventually makes you lose your customers&amp;rsquo; trust.&lt;br /&gt;
For example, around 50% of internet users say that website design is vital in formulating an opinion about a brand. Similarly, another study shows that first impressions of websites are 94% related to design. That means your design takes the lead in engaging the web users. Further, your website design takes part in creating your brand identity and also the sales funnel.&lt;br /&gt;
You surely want to get and maintain all good opi...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-11-03T04:15:31+00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>关于域名和主机的知识你需要了解些什么</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/what-you-need-to-know-about-domains-and-hosting" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2217629</id>
<author>
<name>Abul Kalam Azad Rumon</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                When it comes to building a website, it is important to have a clear understanding of the difference between a domain name and web hosting. These two elements are crucial for establishing a successful online presence. In this comprehensive guide, we will explore the definitions, functions, and interrelationship of domain names and web hosting, providing you with the knowledge needed to make informed decisions about your website.&lt;br /&gt;
What is a Domain Name?&lt;br /&gt;
A domain name serves as the address of your website on the internet. It is the unique identifier that allows users to locate your website easily. Think of it as the equivalent of a street address for your online presence. Just as a street address directs people to a specific location, a domain name directs internet users to your website.&lt;br /&gt;
A domain name typically consists of two parts: the name itself and the extension. For example, the domain name for Google is "google.com." The name can be customized to align with your brand and its pu...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-11-01T10:25:43+00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>做出正确选择：单页应用程序 vs 多页应用程序开发</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/making-the-right-choice-single-page-vs-multi-page-application-development" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2217537</id>
<author>
<name>Aditya Jani</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                &lt;br /&gt;
Websites with well-optimized user flow can witness an impressive 200% increase in conversion rate. So, user flow isn&amp;rsquo;t just a buzzword &amp;mdash; it&amp;rsquo;s the heartbeat of online success. Therefore, when venturing into web application development, whether for browsers or mobile platforms, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to recognize the existence of two fundamental design patterns: the single-page approach and its counterpart, the multi-page structure.&lt;br /&gt;
Here, we will delve deep into the intricacies of user flow, exploring how the choice between these architectures can sculpt seamless, intuitive pathways for your audience.&lt;br /&gt;
SPA vs MPA: Comparison of User Experience&lt;br /&gt;
The comparison of user experience between SPAs and MPAs underscores the importance of speed, fluidity, and responsiveness in modern web applications. Let&amp;rsquo;s check this difference!&lt;br /&gt;
Dynamic Content Loading and Smooth Transitions in SPAs:&lt;br /&gt;
Single Page Applications (SPAs) revolutionized the web by introducing dynamic content loa...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-11-01T09:23:11+00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>揭秘显示分辨率：了解技术中的“K”</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/demystifying-display-resolutions-understanding-the-k-in-tech" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2217084</id>
<author>
<name>Kelly</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                In the world of technology, especially when it comes to TVs and computer monitors, the use of the letter 'K' can be a source of confusion. Terms like 2K, 4K, and 8K are often thrown around, leading consumers to believe that these values represent specific resolutions and dimensions. However, the reality is far from straightforward.&lt;br /&gt;
What Exactly is 'K'?&lt;br /&gt;
First and foremost, it's crucial to understand that the 'K' in these terms simply refers to the number of horizontal pixels on a screen, and it's roughly equivalent to a thousand pixels. Therefore, a 2K display has around 2,000 horizontal pixels, while a 4K display boasts approximately 4,000.&lt;br /&gt;
The confusion arises because the number of 'K's a display has doesn't tell you much else about the display. For instance, a 1920x1080 display, often referred to as Full HD or 1080p, can technically be called 2K. However, few people use this term in practice. Instead, 2K is more commonly associated with 2560x1440, despite the horizontal resolution be...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-10-31T15:33:00+00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>玻璃基板在高性能CPU中的重要性</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/the-importance-of-glass-substrates-in-high-performance-cpus" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2217081</id>
<author>
<name>Jacob Enderson</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                When you think of high-performance CPUs, your mind likely races to the marvel of shrinking transistors over the years. This technological feat allows us to cram an extraordinary number of transistors onto a single chip, leading to more powerful and efficient processors. However, there's more to the story than just the transistors. The substrate that the processor die sits on plays a crucial role in the performance of CPUs. This article delves into the significance of substrates and the shift from traditional epoxy and fiberglass to glass-based substrates, especially as pursued by Intel.&lt;br /&gt;
The Unsung Hero: Substrates&lt;br /&gt;
Substrates are often the unsung heroes in the world of CPU design. Not only do they provide structural support to the delicate processor die, but they also serve as the medium for carrying signals and connecting the die to other components within the system. Traditionally, the substrate material of choice for most CPUs has been a combination of epoxy and fiberglass, which is...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-10-31T15:27:00+00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>ChatGPT API 密钥：释放对话型人工智能的力量</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/chatgpt-api-key-unlock-the-power-of-conversational-ai" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2214678</id>
<author>
<name>Jeff Smith</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                ChatGPT is a large language model chatbot developed by OpenAI. It is known for its ability to generate human-quality text and engage in conversations with users. ChatGPT is currently in beta, but OpenAI has released an API that allows developers to integrate ChatGPT into their own applications.&lt;br /&gt;
The ChatGPT API is a powerful tool that can be used to create a variety of innovative applications, such as chatbots, virtual assistants, and educational tools. However, to use the API, you need to obtain a ChatGPT API key.&lt;br /&gt;
This blog post will explain how to get a ChatGPT API key and how to use it to access the ChatGPT API. We will also discuss some of the potential applications of the ChatGPT API.&lt;br /&gt;
How to Get a ChatGPT API Key?&lt;br /&gt;
To get a ChatGPT API key, you need to create an account on the OpenAI website. Once you have created an account, you can view your API keys by clicking on the "API Keys" tab in the top menu.&lt;br /&gt;
To generate a new API key, click on the "Create New Secret Key" button. You...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-10-27T11:05:33+00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>为什么投资于SEO是一种长期策略？</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/why-investing-in-seo-is-a-long-term-strategy" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2214651</id>
<author>
<name>Digital</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                SEO Strategy has emerged as a powerful tool for marketing your website or online business. It helps safeguard your basic requirements to stay in the online marketing game. You might be thinking that once you cover all the basics, you can just sit back and enjoy the show as the traffic rolls in on your website.&lt;br /&gt;
However, I want to inform you that SEO is not just about checking off some tasks from your list; it&amp;rsquo;s an ongoing process that keeps evolving.&lt;br /&gt;
That&amp;rsquo;s why experts often refer to SEO strategy as a long-term investment. If you want to truly grasp its essence and understand its long-term role, then you&amp;rsquo;re at the right place. So, let&amp;rsquo;s jump into it and I&amp;rsquo;ll explain why investing in SEO is a long-term strategy.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
About SEO &amp;ndash; An Overview&lt;br /&gt;
SEO, which stands for Search Engine Optimization, is a term that may seem technical, but it&amp;rsquo;s quite straightforward. Simply put, it&amp;rsquo;s a system that helps you attract more visitors to your website by mak...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-10-27T10:46:44+00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>如何使用Web3.js调用合约函数

首先，您需要确保已经安装了Web3.js库并将其导入到您的项目中。

接下来，您需要连接到您的以太坊节点。您可以使用`Web3`类的`setProvider`方法来设置提供程序。例如，如果您使用的是Infura节点，您可以将其作为提供程序设置： `web3.eth.setProvider(new web3.providers.HttpProvider('https://ropsten.infura.io/v3/YOUR_INFURA_PROJECT_ID'))`。

一旦连接到节点，您需要加载您的合约。您可以使用ABI（Application Binary Interface）和合约地址来加载合约。例如：
```
var contractABI = YOUR_CONTRACT_ABI;
var contractAddress = YOUR_CONTRACT_ADDRESS;
var contract = new web3.eth.Contract(contractABI, contractAddress);
```

现在，您可以使用`contract.methods`对象来调用您的合约函数。例如，如果您的合约定义了一个名为`myFunction`的函数，并且该函数不接收任何参数，您可以这样调用它：
```
contract.methods.myFunction().call((error, result) =&gt; {
  if(!error) {
    console.log(result);
  } else {
    console.error(error);
  }
});
```

如果您的合约函数需要接收参数，您可以将其传递给调用函数。例如，如果您的函数需要一个字符串参数`param1`和一个整数参数`param2`：
```
contract.methods.myFunction(param1, param2).call((error, result) =&gt; {
  // 处理返回结果或错误
});
```

注意，`call`方法将只读地调用合约函数，即它不会修改区块链状态。如果您需要发送交易来修改状态，您需要使用`send`方法。

这就是如何使用Web3.js调用合约函数的一般步骤。当然，具体的实现可能因项目而异，但这应该给您一个起点来开始使用Web3.js与以太坊合约进行交互。</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/how-to-use-a-web3js-call-contract-function" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2214584</id>
<author>
<name>Oodles Blockchain</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                What is Web3.js in Blockchain Development?&lt;br /&gt;
Web3.js is a JavaScript library that provides a way to interact with Ethereum-based applications. For&amp;nbsp;smart contract development, it allows developers to send transactions, interact with smart contracts, and access Ethereum accounts from JavaScript applications.&lt;br /&gt;
Web3.js provides a set of APIs that allow developers to interact with Ethereum-based applications. These APIs include:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Web3: The main interface for interacting with Ethereum. It provides functions for interacting with accounts, contracts, and the Ethereum network.&lt;br /&gt;
Eth: An interface for interacting with the Ethereum network. It provides functions for sending transactions and querying the network.&lt;br /&gt;
Contract: An interface for interacting with&amp;nbsp;smart contracts. It provides functions for deploying, interacting with, and listening to events from smart contracts.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Below are the steps to Use a Web3.js Call Contract Function:&lt;br /&gt;
1. Install Web3.js &amp;mdash; Web3.js is a JavaScript...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-10-27T10:10:04+00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>折叠腕式手机：摩托罗拉展示疯狂的概念</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/foldable-cell-phone-for-the-wrist-motorola-shows-crazy-concept" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2213159</id>
<author>
<name>Kelly</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                Motorola presented an unusual foldable concept at Lenovo Tech World. It is a smartphone with a flexible display that can be worn on the wrist. According to Motorola, the "Adaptive Display Concept" opens up completely new possibilities.&lt;br /&gt;
Motorola presents futuristic smartwatch phone&lt;br /&gt;
We already know one or the other foldable smartphone from Motorola. But what the brand of the parent company Lenovo has now presented, even the competition from Samsung, Huawei, Oppo and Google cannot offer. The "Adaptive Display Concept", as it is called so far, can be bent around the own wrist. It is a mixture of smartphone and smartwatch.&lt;br /&gt;
According to Motorola, the Android gadget can be used like a normal smartphone with a 6.9-inch display when unfolded. Wrapped around the wrist, however, the wearer has a smartwatch with a customized 4.3-inch screen. Only the visible part of the display is used in this case, according to the manufacturer.&lt;br /&gt;
If the smartwatch smartphone is on the wrist, an AI ensures individu...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-10-25T14:40:00+00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>在Windows中，通过附近共享功能简化数据共享</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/simplifying-data-sharing-with-nearby-sharing-in-windows" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2213157</id>
<author>
<name>Jacob Enderson</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                Introduction&lt;br /&gt;
Transferring data between devices within your home network should be straightforward, right? However, the reality often involves dealing with flash drives, messy cords, and complex network setups. Fortunately, recent versions of Windows have introduced a feature called Nearby Sharing, aimed at simplifying data transfer without the need for extra steps. In this article, we'll explore how to use Nearby Sharing and its requirements.&lt;br /&gt;
System Requirements&lt;br /&gt;
Before you can take advantage of Nearby Sharing, there are some prerequisites you need to meet:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Operating System: Nearby Sharing is available in Windows 11 and Windows 10 (version 1803 or later). If you're using Windows 10, ensure you've run the necessary Windows updates to access this feature.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Bluetooth: Your computer must have Bluetooth 4.0 or later with Low Energy (LE) support. To check if your system supports Low Energy, go to Device Manager, find your Bluetooth adapter, and look for a listing under "Details" that says...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-10-25T14:35:00+00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>在网站开发中，REST API有什么独特之处？</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/what-makes-rest-api-unique-in-website-development" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2212279</id>
<author>
<name>Alex</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                APIs found an innovative way to interact between different sources and servers to represent them on websites and applications. These may include live news, updates and live broadcasts.&lt;br /&gt;
These applications work by requesting a certain type of data from the source and receiving them to the backlog of the website, while developers and designers control how this information is streamed on the front end.&lt;br /&gt;
There are several protocols and applications used that serve different purposes. However, REST APIs stand out from the rest because they have a distinguished information structure and control compared to other types. Let&amp;rsquo;s discover how these APIs work and what makes them unique.&lt;br /&gt;
Defining RESTful APIs&lt;br /&gt;
Representational state transfer application programming interfaces, or REST APIs, use HTTP standards to request and receive data from sources and consoles and organise them in XML and JSON files, making data representation more sophisticated and comprehensive.&lt;br /&gt;
This way, developers can...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-10-24T11:34:20+00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>探索雷电5：连接性的未来</title>
<link href="https://techplanet.today/post/exploring-thunderbolt-5-the-future-of-connectivity" rel="alternate"/>
<id>https://techplanet.today/2211097</id>
<author>
<name>Jacob Enderson</name>
</author>
<summary type="html">
                The tech world is abuzz with excitement as the latest in connectivity standards takes center stage. USB-C enthusiasts have a lot to look forward to, as not only is the iPhone embracing this technology, but there's also a new contender in town - Thunderbolt 5. Thunderbolt 5, which utilizes the USB-C connector, promises lightning-fast data transfer speeds, but its true competition isn't what you might expect.&lt;br /&gt;
Thunderbolt's Evolution&lt;br /&gt;
You might be wondering why Thunderbolt 5 is generating so much buzz, especially when its predecessor, Thunderbolt 4, was considered a powerhouse. To understand its significance, we need to delve into the world of USB and Thunderbolt connectivity.&lt;br /&gt;
Thunderbolt 4, although impressive, is no longer the reigning champion of high-speed data transfer. Thunderbolt 5 has set its sights on a new contender: USB 4v2. Thunderbolt 5's key goal is to surpass USB 4v2 in both data transfer speeds and power delivery capabilities. At first glance, Thunderbolt 5 might appear sim...
            </summary>
<updated>2023-10-21T18:11:00+00:00</updated>
</entry>
</feed>